The cell volume is very important for an oocyte and
卵子の体積は非常に大きく、
very small for a spermatozoon.
精子の体積は非常に小さいです。
We can say that the ovum is in a state of dilatation, it is completely in
卵子は拡張しており、完全に開いており、完全にいわゆる
a state of openness, it is completely what we call in extension.
伸展していると言えます。
It is open, while the spermatozoon, on the other hand, is in internal
開いているのに対し、精子は内旋しています。
rotation.
内旋しています。
It is desiccated, it is mummified.
乾燥しており、ミイラ化しています。
However, the DNA concentration is very important for
一方、DNA濃度は精子にとって非常に重要です。
the spermatozoon, in DNA.
精子にとって、DNA濃度は非常に重要です。
The mobility, however, of the oocyte.
一方、卵子の可動性。
The spermatozoon, it is completely arrested.
精子は完全に停止しています。
The number of these...
これらの数...
produced is approximately 400. This means that primary oocytes,
生産されるのは約400個です。つまり、一次卵母細胞は
they are formed during the fetal
胎児期に形成されます。
period. In other words, when you were in your mother's womb, you
言い換えれば、お母さんのお腹の中にいたとき、あなたはすでに
were already busy
自分の卵子を
producing your own oocytes. The nurse cells, the follicular cells,
作っていました。栄養細胞、卵胞細胞は、
I will
私はあなたに
So one is transmitted by development and one is given by the
したがって、一方は発生によって伝達され、もう一方は
mother, which will provide axes.
母から与えられ、軸を形成します。
This means that it is already a pathway for transmitting information at the genetic level,
これは、遺伝的レベル、エピジェネティックなタイプ、世代を超えた形成に関する情報を伝えるための道筋がすでに存在することを意味します。
of epigenetic type, of transgenerational formation.
エピジェネティックなタイプ、世代を超えた形成に関する情報を伝えるための道筋がすでに存在することを意味します。
The ovaries need to be internal because they must be heated,
卵巣は温められる必要があるため、体内に留まる必要があります。
they need to be warm, whereas the testes are...
温められる必要があるのに対し、精巣は...
descended, because they need to be a bit cooler.
下に降りて、少し涼しくする必要があるからです。
This is important when we have women presenting with fertility problems.
不妊症の問題を抱える女性が来院する際には、これは重要です。
Sometimes, when you work at the sacrum level, you can feel a coldness.
時には、仙骨のレベルで作業していると、冷たさを感じることがあります。
This can be a problem.
それは問題かもしれません。
Here, we will discuss it in relation to the duodenum, in relation to the arteries and what
ここでは、十二指腸、動脈、そして
we call plicae, fossae.
いわゆるひだ、くぼみについて話します。
of folds at the level of the duodenum that transmit trophic information
十二指腸のひだは、栄養情報を
via the arterial system, among others, via the ovarian arterial systems
動脈系を介して、特に卵巣動脈系を介して、
or testicular arteries,
または精巣動脈系を介して伝達します。
it will all depend, where fertility must be treated much higher up
すべては、不妊治療がはるかに高いレベルで、
on the framework of the pancreatic facial pentagon.
膵臓の顔面五角形の枠組みの中で行われるかどうかにかかっています。